acontinuouslean.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy | A Continuous Lean.

This notice explains the on-line information privacy policy practices of Earnest Western Reserve, Inc. (â€œACLâ€) so that you may make choices as to how to use our website. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information as described in this notice. We recommend that you review this notice from time to time to see if it has changed. Your continued use of our site is your acceptance of our privacy policy.

**Use and Purpose of Collected Information** – Our website does not collect any personal information about you other than the information that you intentionally submit to us by completing and sending a form on our website, by submitting email to us, or by logging onto one of the areas of our website that is restricted to registered users.

ACL will use this information in connection with processing your inquiries and request and/or to help improve our products and services. ACL intends to share such information with third parties outside of ACL, including its affiliated manufacturers and service providers.

**IP Addresses** – We do not collect any information about users who are merely browsing through our website. However, if you request a page from our website or download any information, our servers will log your current IP address. An IP address is automatically assigned to your computer every time you browse the Internet. We do not link IP addresses to any personal information about you. We will see your e-mail address only if you give it to us by filling out a form or by sending us an e-mail message or if you are a registered user.

**Cookies** – Our website may use â€œcookiesâ€ to process and store information relevant to your use of our websites and services. Cookies are identifiers that a website can send to your browser to keep on your computer to identify you and make your successive visits to the website more efficient. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie. This will give you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

**User Information** – In our effort to provide personalization and some services, we may at times ask you to submit information about yourself. You never have to answer these questions. However, if you should elect to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with some of the services dependent upon the collection of this information.

We may use your personal information to send you e-mails and certain marketing communications that we think may be of interest to you, such as new product offerings and/or technical updates. You may stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from ACL by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive.

**Links** – Our website may contain links to other sites. ACL is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites. Please refer to the policies of the respective site(s).

**Submissions** – Anything that you post or upload to our website (â€œSubmissionâ€) is understood to be non-confidential and non-proprietary. You have no expectation of privacy and ACL has no obligation of privacy with respect to any Submission. Furthermore, ACL is not responsible for the use and/or treatment of your Submission made by ACL’s affiliated manufacturers and service providers. Prior to making any Submission you acknowledge that (1) your Submission is not owned or claimed to be owned by a third party or that it infringes the patent, copyright, trademark, or other intellectual property rights of another and (2) you will hold ACL harmless from any liability incurred with or arising from such Submission.
